Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files
    - Speck, Christa (Box A-111, Folder 221)
    - Spector, Jack (Box A-111, Folder 222)
    - Spector, Myles S. (Box A-111, Folder 223)
    - Spector, Ronnie + the Ronettes (Box A-111, Folder 224)
    - Speed, Carol (Box A-111, Folder 225)
    - Speed, Constance (Box A-111, Folder 226)
    - Speed, Dennis (Box A-111, Folder 227)
    - Speed, Ivy (Box A-111, Folder 228)
    - Speed, Morris (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-111, Folder 229)
    - Speed, Winnifred (Box A-111, Folder 230)
    - Spell, George (Box A-111, Folder 231)
    - Spellen, Suzanne (Box A-111, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: Sam Rodriguez
    - Speller, James (Box A-111, Folder 233)
    - Speller, Lonnie (Box A-111, Folder 234)
      Photographer if identified: Jay Sharp
    - Spellman, Blondell (Box A-111, Folder 235)
    - Spellman, Francis (Cardinal) (Box A-111, Folder 236)
    - Spellman, Guy (Box A-111, Folder 237)
    - Spellman, Mitchell W. (Box A-111, Folder 238)
    - Spellman, Robert (Dr.) (Box A-111, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: Peter L. Gould (Essex County College)
    - Spells, Wayne (Box A-111, Folder 240)
    - Spelman College (Box A-111, Folder 241)
    - Spence, Alberta L. (Box A-111, Folder 242)
    - Spence, Bevin A. (Box A-111, Folder 243)
    - Spence, Robert (Box A-111, Folder 244)
    - Spence, Trevor (Box A-111, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, King Photographers, YMCA of Greater NY P.R. Dept., Ace Creative Photos
    - Spencer, Barbara (Box A-111, Folder 246)
    - Spencer, Carl (Box A-111, Folder 247)
    - Spencer, Chandler (Box A-111, Folder 248)
      Photographer if identified: Lensman
    - Spencer, Christine (Box A-111, Folder 249)
      Photographer if identified: J. Abresch
    - Spencer, Dave (Box A-111, Folder 250)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James Gilbert, Tex Harris, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Spencer, Dorothy (Mrs.) (Box A-111, Folder 251)
    - Spencer, Edna (Box A-111, Folder 252)
    - Spencer, Edward (Box A-111, Folder 253)
    - Spencer, George C. (Box A-111, Folder 254)
    - Spencer, James (Box A-111, Folder 255)
    - Spencer, Janice (Box A-111, Folder 256)
    - Spencer, Jeanette (Box A-111, Folder 257)
    - Spencer, John H. (Box A-111, Folder 258)
    - Spencer, John W. (Box A-111, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Sid Lane
    - Spencer, Kenneth (Box A-111, Folder 260)
    - Spencer, Madra (Box A-111, Folder 261)
    - Spencer, Armistan + Glenda (Box A-111, Folder 262)
    - Spencer, Otha (Ms.) (Box A-111, Folder 263)
    - Spencer, Patrick (Box A-111, Folder 264)
    - Spencer, Ronald D. (Box A-111, Folder 265)
    - Spencer, Scott S. (Box A-111, Folder 266)
    - Spencer, Shields (Box A-111, Folder 267)
      Prints taped together.
    - Spencer, Thelma (Box A-111, Folder 268)
    - Spencer, Tony (Box A-111, Folder 269)
    - Spencer, Veronica (Box A-111, Folder 270)
    - Sperling, Gary H. (Box A-111, Folder 271)
    - Spex, Aleida (Box A-111, Folder 272)
    - Spiderman (Box A-111, Folder 273)
      Photographer if identified: Marc Becker
    - Spiderwoman Theater (Box A-111, Folder 274)
    - Spiegel, Samuel A. (Judge) (Box A-111, Folder 275)
      Photographer if identified: Conway Studios
    - Spigner, Brenda (Box A-111, Folder 276)
    - Spinelli, Tony (Box A-111, Folder 277)
    - Spingarn, Arthur (Box A-111, Folder 278)
    - Spinks, Leon (Box A-111, Folder 279)
    - Spinks, Michael (Box A-111, Folder 280)
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin, Dave Greene
    - Spinners, The (Box A-111, Folder 281)
      Also six velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann, George West
    - Gil-Smythe, Harry (Box A-111, Folder 282)
    - Springer, Marva (Box A-111, Folder 283)
    - Spiro, Roxanne (Box A-112, Folder 1)
    - Spivers, Marks (Box A-112, Folder 2)
    - Spivey, Charles (Box A-112, Folder 3)
    - Spivey, John J (Box A-112, Folder 4)
    - Spivey, Victoria (Box A-112, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Jim Pells
    - Spock, Benjamin Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 6)
    - Spo-De-Odee (Box A-112, Folder 7)
    - Sponono (Box A-112, Folder 8)
    - Spook who sat by the door (Box A-112, Folder 9)
      Also three typescript leaves.
    - Spooner, Ezvick (Box A-112, Folder 10)
    - Spooner, Keith (Box A-112, Folder 11)
    - Spooner, William (Box A-112, Folder 12)
    - Spottwswood, Stephen G Bishop (Box A-112, Folder 13)
      Also 2 velox prints and one typescript leaf.
    - Spradley, Gloria J. (Box A-112, Folder 14)
    - Spradley, Theodore R (Box A-112, Folder 15)
    - Spraggins, Stweart (Box A-112, Folder 16)
    - Sprague, Peter (Box A-112, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Ginsburg
    - Spratley, James A. (Box A-112, Folder 18)
    - Spriggs, Bernard A. (Box A-112, Folder 19)
    - Spriggs, Ed (Box A-112, Folder 20)
    - Springer, Ashton (Box A-112, Folder 21)
    - Springfield, Equites, Ltd (Box A-112, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: Taylor Made Photo
    - Spruill, Deborah Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 23)
    - Spruill, James (Box A-112, Folder 24)
    - Spruill, John (Box A-112, Folder 25)
    - Spry, Fred 1st Sgt (Box A-112, Folder 26)
    - Spurlock, Welburt L Jr (Box A-112, Folder 27)
    - Spurlock, Marshall (Box A-112, Folder 28)
      Photographer if identified: Robert L. Reily
    - Squardon, Howard M. (Box A-112, Folder 29)
    - St. Jacques, Raymond (Box A-112, Folder 30)
      Also one typescript leaf.
    - St. John, Hary (Box A-112, Folder 31)
    - St. John Keisha (Box A-112, Folder 32)
      Photographer if identified: Raymond Ross
    - St. Johns Hotpital (Box A-112, Folder 33)
    - Stacy, Azie BM Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 34)
    - Stackhouse, Anne Bishop (Box A-112, Folder 35)
    - Stackhouse, William E. (Box A-112, Folder 36)
    - Shafford, Eddie (Box A-112, Folder 37)
    - Stafford, Essie R (Box A-112, Folder 38)
    - Stafford, Wm H (Box A-112, Folder 39)
      Also 3 velox prints and one halftone print.
    - Stafford, Yvonne (Box A-112, Folder 40)
    - Stage 2 (Box A-112, Folder 41)
    - Stagger, Roy Mr & Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 42)
    - Stagger, Mary E Rev. (Box A-112, Folder 43)
    - Stainback, Shelia (Box A-112, Folder 44)
    - Stairsteper (Box A-112, Folder 45)
    - Stalks, Larrie (Box A-112, Folder 46)
    - Stalks, Larry West Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 47)
    - Stallworth, Annette L Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 48)
    - Stallwortz, Granwill (Box A-112, Folder 49)
    - Stallworth, Dave (Box A-112, Folder 50)
    - Stallworth, Doris (Box A-112, Folder 51)
      Photographer if identified: King Photos
    - Stallworth, Dottie (Box A-112, Folder 52)
    - Stallworth, John (Box A-112, Folder 53)
    - Stamiaton, Ruth (Box A-112, Folder 54)
    - Stamp, US Post Serivce (Box A-112, Folder 55)
    - Stamps CS (Box A-112, Folder 56)
      5 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Bro David McAdams,Harris Photo
    - Stamps, Ed (Box A-112, Folder 57)
    - Stamps, James E (Box A-112, Folder 58)
    - Stapms, Leotta (Box A-112, Folder 59)
    - Stapms, Phil (Box A-112, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: Gen Greene
    - Stanback, Elaine (Box A-112, Folder 61)
    - Stancell, Arnold (Box A-112, Folder 62)
    - Standard, Kenneth G (Box A-112, Folder 63)
    - Standifer, James Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: Pubic Relations
    - Standfield, Andrews (Box A-112, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: Jan W Faul, Negro Press, Cecil Layne,
    - Stanford, Carolyn (Box A-112, Folder 66)
    - Standford, Helen Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 67)
    - Standford, Olivia (Box A-112, Folder 68)
    - Stanis, Bernnadette (Box A-112, Folder 69)
    - Stanislaus, Bernadette (Box A-112, Folder 70)
    - Stanislaus, Lamule Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 71)
    - Stanislaus, Galen Dr (Box A-112, Folder 72)
    - Stacke, Clarence (Box A-112, Folder 73)
    - Stanley Arthur (Box A-112, Folder 74)
    - Stanley, Clarence (Box OS-1, Folder 1)
    - Stanley, Frank L (Box A-112, Folder 75)
    - Stanle Ida, Mrs. (Box A-112, Folder 76)
    - Stanley, Jr Frank L (Box A-112, Folder 77)
    - Stanley, Frank L Sr. (Box A-112, Folder 78)
    - Stanley, James (Box A-112, Folder 79)
    - Stanley, Laurence (Box A-112, Folder 80)
    - Stanley, Lonnie (Box A-112, Folder 81)
    - Staton, Dakota (Box A-112, Folder 82)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick
    - Stanley, W Sterling (Box A-112, Folder 83)
    - Stanbury, william (Box A-112, Folder 84)
    - Stanton, Ellsworth G. (Box A-112, Folder 85)
      Photographer if identified: Bela Cseh
    - Stanton, Freda (Box A-112, Folder 86)
    - Stanton, Frederick G (Box A-112, Folder 87)
    - Stanton, Joe (Box A-112, Folder 88)
    - Stanton, LH (Box A-112, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Blackstone
    - Stanton, Larry (Box A-112, Folder 90)
    - Stanton, Sonny (Box A-112, Folder 91)
    - Staple Singers (Box A-112, Folder 92)
      Also two typescript leaves and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: DM Wallace, Epic Records
    - Staples, Mavis (Box A-112, Folder 93)
    - Stapleton, Maureen (Box A-112, Folder 94)
    - Star of David (Box A-112, Folder 95)
      One print is mounted.
    - Star Trek (Box A-112, Folder 96)
    - Starburst Records (Box A-112, Folder 97)
    - Stargell, Willie (Box A-112, Folder 98)
    - Stars (Box A-112, Folder 99)
    - Standard, Edwards (Box A-112, Folder 100)
    - Starfires (Box A-112, Folder 101)
    - Stargard (Box A-112, Folder 101a)
    - Stargell, Willie (Box A-112, Folder 102)
    - Stark, Abe (Box A-112, Folder 103)
      Photographer if identified: Ross Photo, Whitestone, Ace Creative, Bill Mitchell
    - Starke, Margaret (Box A-112, Folder 104)
    - Stark, Mary (Box A-112, Folder 105)
    - Starks, Jonathan (Box A-112, Folder 106)
    - Starks, John (Box A-112, Folder 107)
    - Starks, Marshall (Box A-112, Folder 108)
    - Starks, Renee (Box A-112, Folder 109)
    - Starlighters (Box A-112, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo
    - Starr, Edwin (Box A-112, Folder 111)
    - Starr, Maretha (Box A-112, Folder 112)
    - Starette (Box A-112, Folder 113)
    - Star Scape Singers (Box A-112, Folder 114)
    - Stare of faith gospel sings (Box A-112, Folder 115)
    - State Building Ground Breaking (Box A-112, Folder 116)
      Also 4 velox prints and one computer-printed typescript leaf.
      Photographer if identified: News Voice International, Harris Photo, News Voice International, Johnson Hancard, James Gilbert,
    - State Building Ground Breaking (Box A-112, Folder 117)
    - Staten, Randolp W. (Box A-112, Folder 118)
    - Staton, Bill (Box A-112, Folder 119)
    - Staton, Candi (Box A-112, Folder 120)
    - Staton, Dakota (Box A-112, Folder 121)
    - Staton, Dionne (Box A-112, Folder 122)
    - Staton, John U (Box A-112, Folder 123)
    - Staton, Lori- Anne (Box A-112, Folder 124)
    - Staton, Walter C Jr. (Box A-112, Folder 125)
    - Statue of Liberty (Box A-112, Folder 126)
      Photographer if identified: The Port of New York Authority
    - Stauffer, Thomas (Box A-112, Folder 127)
    - Staunback, Howard Dr (Box A-112, Folder 128)
    - Staunton, Kim (Box A-112, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Susan Cook
    - Staunton, Mary B (Box A-112, Folder 130)
    - Staupers, Mabel K Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 131)
    - Stautet, H.C (Mrs) (Box A-112, Folder 132)
    - Stax, Organization (Box A-112, Folder 133)
    - Steber, Ruth (Box A-112, Folder 134)
    - Steel Bands (Box A-112, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Amsterdamn,
    - Steel Pulse (Box A-112, Folder 136)
    - Stelle, Annie (Box A-112, Folder 137)
    - Steele, Frank + Sons (Box A-112, Folder 138)
    - Steele, Gary (Box A-112, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: H. Cooper, United Press International
    - Steele, Joseph Sr. (Box A-112, Folder 140)
    - Steele, Joy (Box A-112, Folder 141)
    - Steele, Larry (Box A-112, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Fred Hess & Son
    - Steele, Lorenzo (Box A-112, Folder 143)
    - Steele, Richard (Box A-112, Folder 144)
    - Steers, Joan (Box A-112, Folder 145)
    - Steete, Frank E Dr (Box A-112, Folder 146)
    - Stein, Andrew (Box A-112, Folder 147)
    - Stein, David NBA Comm (Box A-112, Folder 148)
    - Steingut, Bob (Box A-112, Folder 149)
    - Steingut, Stanley (Box A-112, Folder 150)
    - Stennett, Erana (Box A-112, Folder 151)
    - Stennett, Linda (Box A-112, Folder 152)
    - Stennette Perry J (Box A-112, Folder 153)
    - Stenson, John (Box A-112, Folder 154)
    - Stent, Madelon Delany Dr (Box A-112, Folder 155)
    - Step, Marc (Box A-112, Folder 156)
      Photographer if identified: Junebug Clark
    - Step, Lively (Box A-112, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Carl Samrock
    - Stephens, Ana M. (Box A-112, Folder 158)
    - Stephens Arthur L (Box A-112, Folder 159)
    - Stephens Bernce (Box A-112, Folder 160)
    - Stephens, Bill (Box A-112, Folder 161)
    - Stephens, Bill (Box A-112, Folder 162)
    - Stephens, Brooke (Box A-112, Folder 163)
    - Stephens, Cortez D. (Box A-112, Folder 164)
    - Stephens, Diane (Box A-112, Folder 165)
    - Stephens, Esme (Box A-112, Folder 166)
    - Stephens, Ingrid (Box A-112, Folder 167)
    - Stephens, Jacquenlyn Dr (Box A-112, Folder 168)
    - Stephens, Phy (Box A-112, Folder 169)
    - Stephens, Ray (Box A-112, Folder 170)
    - Stephens, Sylvia (Box A-112, Folder 171)
    - Stephens, Vernon (Box A-112, Folder 172)
    - Stephens, Walter (Box A-112, Folder 173)
    - Stephens, Williams W (Box A-112, Folder 174)
    - Stephens, Ashton G. (Box A-112, Folder 175)
    - Stephens, Barbara (Box A-112, Folder 176)
    - Stephens, Beril V. (Box A-112, Folder 177)
    - Stephenson, Jeanette (Box A-112, Folder 178)
    - Stephensons, Vivlet E Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 179)
    - Stepp, Marc (Box A-112, Folder 180)
      Photographer if identified: Joe Clarke
    - Steptoe, John (Box A-112, Folder 181)
    - Sterett, John (Box A-112, Folder 182)
    - Sterling, HS (Box A-112, Folder 183)
    - Sterrilization Case (Box A-112, Folder 184)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Intr Press Photo
    - Sterling, Challe A (Box A-112, Folder 185)
    - Sterling, Charles (Box A-112, Folder 186)
    - Sterling, Mckinley (Box A-112, Folder 187)
    - Sterling, Productions (Box A-112, Folder 188)
    - Stern, Henry (Box A-112, Folder 189)
    - Stern, Isaac (Box A-112, Folder 190)
    - Sterner, John (Box A-112, Folder 191)
    - Sterrett, John F. (Box A-112, Folder 192)
    - Stevens, Aliie M Mrs. (Box A-112, Folder 193)
    - Stevens, Carole T Mrs. (Box A-112, Folder 194)
    - Stevens, Claude L Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: World Wide Photos
    - Stevens, Ella M (Box A-112, Folder 196)
    - Stevens, Esme (Box A-112, Folder 197)
      Photographer if identified: Lab Inc
    - Stevens, Gary (Box A-112, Folder 198)
    - Stevens, George (Box A-112, Folder 199)
    - Stevens, Harold Judy (Box A-112, Folder 200)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, James Gilbert, James Heffernan,
    - Stevens, Harold A Mrs. (Box A-112, Folder 201)
    - Stevens, Jeannette Joyce (Box A-112, Folder 202)
    - Steven, John (Box A-112, Folder 203)
    - Steven, Jose (Box A-112, Folder 204)
    - Stevens, Lionel (Box A-112, Folder 205)
    - Steven, Lorice (Box A-112, Folder 206)
    - Steven, Margaret (Box A-112, Folder 207)
    - Steven, Mildred (Box A-112, Folder 208)
    - Steven, Nathaneil (Box A-112, Folder 209)
    - Stevens, Roger L (Box A-112, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: Richard Braaten
    - Stevens, Ronald smokey (Box A-112, Folder 211)
    - Stevens, Rose M (Box A-112, Folder 212)
    - Stevens, Sharron (Box A-112, Folder 213)
    - Stevens, Preston (Box A-112, Folder 214)
    - Stevens, Eddy A (Box A-112, Folder 215)
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box A-112, Folder 216)
      Three paper stereotype matrices, one halftone print, and three negatives containing six images.
      Photographer if identified: Jan Studios, International News Photo, Layne Studio, James C. Campbell, James Gilbert
    - Stevenson, Bethel (Box A-112, Folder 217)
    - Stevenson, Blossom (Box A-112, Folder 218)
    - Stevenson, Bobby (Box A-112, Folder 219)
    - Stevenson, Denise (Box A-112, Folder 220)
    - Stevenson, Don (Box A-112, Folder 221)
    - Stevenson, Dorothy (Box A-112, Folder 222)
    - Stevenson, Edward (Box A-112, Folder 223)
    - Stevenson, Edward Sr. (Box A-112, Folder 224)
    - Stevenson, Jerome (Box A-112, Folder 225)
    - Stevenson, Jerry and Anna (Box A-112, Folder 226)
    - Stevenson, John (Box A-112, Folder 227)
    - Stevenson, Ron (Box A-112, Folder 228)
    - Steverman, Michael (Box A-112, Folder 229)
    - Steward, Ellen (Box A-112, Folder 230)
    - Steward, Norma (Box A-112, Folder 231)
    - Steward Susan M Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 232)
      One illustration.
    - Steward, Tina (Box A-112, Folder 233)
    - Stewart, Aaron (Box A-112, Folder 234)
    - Stewart, Al (Box A-112, Folder 235)
    - Stewart, Albert C Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 236)
    - Stewart, Amii (Box A-112, Folder 237)
    - Stwart, Anne Mrs (Box A-112, Folder 238)
    - Stewart, Antene (Box A-112, Folder 239)
    - Stewart, Billy (Box A-112, Folder 240)
    - Stewart, Bob (Box A-112, Folder 241)
      Also 5 typescript leaves.
    - Stweart, Cornelus (Box A-112, Folder 242)
    - Stewart Deboeah M (Box A-112, Folder 243)
    - Stewart, Delano (Box A-112, Folder 244)
    - Stewart, Donan (Box A-112, Folder 245)
    - Stewart, Ellan (Box A-112, Folder 246)
    - Stewart, Elmer (Box A-112, Folder 247)
    - Stewart, Florence (Box A-112, Folder 248)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photography
    - Slums (Box A-112, Folder 249)
    - Stewart, Jaddie (Box A-112, Folder 250)
    - Stewart, Jane (Box A-112, Folder 251)
    - Stewart, Jim (Box A-112, Folder 252)
    - Stewart, John (Box A-112, Folder 253)
    - Stewart, John L (Box A-112, Folder 254)
    - Stewart, Joesph Jr (Box A-112, Folder 255)
    - Stewart, Josephine (Box A-112, Folder 256)
    - Stewart, Kenneth (Box A-112, Folder 257)
    - Stewart, Kirk (Box A-112, Folder 258)
    - Stewart, Maeretha (Box A-112, Folder 259)
    - Stewart, Maria (Box A-112, Folder 260)
    - Stewart, Mary L (Box A-112, Folder 261)
    - Stewart, Malcoim (Box A-112, Folder 262)
    - Stewart, Mary, W Mrs. (Box A-112, Folder 263)
    - Stewart, Maurice (Box A-112, Folder 264)
    - Stewart, Mel (Box A-112, Folder 265)
    - Stewart, Meile (Box A-112, Folder 266)
    - Stewart, Mildred (Box A-112, Folder 267)
    - Stewart, Milla M (Box A-112, Folder 268)
    - Stewart, Paul A (Box A-112, Folder 269)
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative
    - Stewart, Philip R Dr. (Box A-112, Folder 270)
    - Stewart, Red (Box A-112, Folder 271)
    - Stewart, Robert (Box A-112, Folder 272)
    - Stewart, Ron (Box A-112, Folder 273)
    - Stewart, Ronald (Box A-113, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Fr. J. Biondi/FDNY
    - Stewart, Sandra (Box A-113, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Sandy (Box A-113, Folder 3)
    - Stewart, Sara Hill (Box A-113, Folder 4)
    - Stewart, Shirley (Box A-113, Folder 5)
    - Stewart, Sloan (Box A-113, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Sofia (Box A-113, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, Thomas D. Jr. (Box A-113, Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Waldaba (Box A-113, Folder 9)
      Also 3 velox prints. 3 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Kingsley W. Grant, Peterkin Photo, Hamilton Associates, King Photographers, Harris Photo, Dave Greene,
    - Stewart, Warren H. Rev. (Box A-113, Folder 10)
    - Stewart, Willard C. (Box A-113, Folder 11)
    - Stewart, Wm. B. Dr. (Box A-113, Folder 12)
    - Stewart, William J. (Box A-113, Folder 13)
    - Stewar, Ava (Box A-113, Folder 14)
    - Stevort, Thomas (Box A-113, Folder 15)
    - Stich-Randall, Teresa (Box A-113, Folder 16)
    - Phyllis T. Stickney (Box A-113, Folder 17)
      Two different indviduals pictured.
    - Stiggers, Valencia (Box A-113, Folder 18)
    - Stiles, Saundra (Box A-113, Folder 19)
    - Still, Larry (Box A-113, Folder 20)
    - Still, William Grant (Box A-113, Folder 21)
    - Stiller, Percy (Box A-113, Folder 22)
    - Stinley, Pernila (Box A-113, Folder 23)
    - Stingley, Connie (Box A-113, Folder 24)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Hicks
    - Stinnette, James P. (Box A-113, Folder 25)
    - Stinson, A. L. Mrs. (Box A-113, Folder 26)
    - Stinson, Bill (Box A-113, Folder 27)
    - Stinson, David B. (Box A-113, Folder 28)
    - Stinson, Harold N. (Box A-113, Folder 29)
    - Stinson, James (Sonny) (Box A-113, Folder 30)
    - Stinson, Nathaniel (Box A-113, Folder 31)
    - Stinson, William (Box A-113, Folder 32)
    - Stint, Wesley (Box A-113, Folder 33)
    - The Stirrers (Box A-113, Folder 34)
    - Stith, Cynthia (Box A-113, Folder 35)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, James Gilbert,
    - Stith, Bishop Forest C. (Box A-113, Folder 36)
    - Stith, Julia (Box A-113, Folder 37)
    - Stith, Julia (Box A-113, Folder 38)
    - Stith, Sam (Box A-113, Folder 39)
    - Stith, Valerie (Box A-113, Folder 40)
    - Stitt, Frances Mrs. (Box A-113, Folder 41)
    - Stitt, Francis See Rector, Shirley (Box A-113, Folder 42)
      1 ms. leaf.
    - Stitt, Sonny (Box A-113, Folder 43)
      2 prints are stuck together with paste. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Jim Alexander, Johnson, Popsie,
    - Stitt, Sonny (Box A-113, Folder 44)
    - Stockand, James (Box A-113, Folder 45)
    - Stockett, Robert Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-113, Folder 46)
    - Stockton, Robert (Box A-113, Folder 47)
    - Stoddard, Reynold (Box A-113, Folder 48)
    - Stokeling, Luke (Box A-113, Folder 49)
      Photographer if identified: A. Cox
    - Stokeley, Hilda (Box A-113, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo
    - Stokeley, Hilda (Box A-113, Folder 51)
    - Stokes, Alvin W. Jr. (Box A-113, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: Lorstan-Thomas
    - Stokes, Bill (Box A-113, Folder 53)
    - Stokes, Carl (Box A-113, Folder 54)
      Also 3 velox prints. 1 print of Kenneth Clement (Stokes' campaign manager.) 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Raymond Ross, Wide World Photos, United Press International, Mark Chester, ASCAP,
    - Stokes, Cassie (Box A-113, Folder 55)
    - Stokes, Colin (Box A-113, Folder 56)
    - Stokes, Donald (Box A-113, Folder 57)
    - Stokes, H. (Box A-113, Folder 58)
    - Stokes, Harvey (Box A-113, Folder 59)
    - Stokes, Isaac Prophet (Box A-113, Folder 60)
    - Stokes, Louis (Box A-113, Folder 61)
      Also 1 laser print
      Photographer if identified: United Press International,
    - Stokes, Olivia Pearl (Box A-113, Folder 62)
      Also 3 velox prints. 1 print stuck to folder.
      Photographer if identified: Pan American World Airways, Samuel E. Walker
    - Stokes, Rembert (Box A-113, Folder 63)
      1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto. One print has staple through edge.
    - Stokes, Stephani (Box A-113, Folder 64)
    - Stokes, Tony "Pee Wee" (Box A-113, Folder 65)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box A-113, Folder 66)
    - Stone, Anthony (Box A-113, Folder 67)
      Photographer if identified: Port of New York Authority
    - Stone Center (Box A-113, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams,
    - Stone, Charles "Chuck" (See Adam Powell - also Black Power Conference) (Box A-113, Folder 69)
      1 print mounted on cardboard. 1 print stuck to folder.